# MATEJ MAŤKULIAK

# • DETAILS •

+421 917 231 549 matej.matkuliak@gmail.com

# LINKS

Example of my work matkuliak.xyz

# SKILLS

Linux

GitHub

JIRA

Confluence

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

**Google Analytics** 

# LANGUAGES

English

# PROFILE

I'd describe myself as a well-rounded technical guy who is quick to learn and adapt to change. Working primarily on writing/content management. Although my experience so far has been that you need a bit more than solid writing to be a good technical writer. Well versed in networking, CI/CD, version control systems, VMs and more.

# EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

# Technical Writer at Frinx, Poprad

July 2021 — May 2022

# **Full time**

- lead on technical documentation, complete overhaul of documentation process
- automated process of building and deploying documentation I used tool Retype, it builds beautiful HTML and CSS from Markdown code
- automated release notes standardization of commit messages together with a script allowed us to pull release notes directly from Github's commit history

# Technical Writer at Frinx, Liptovský Mikuláš

September 2019 — June 2021

#### Part-time

- introduction to real-world software development process CI/CD
- technical documentation creation/management
- · website management (WordPress, ReactJS)
- preparing environment for testing (VMs in Proxmox)

# EDUCATION

# Bachelor's degree, Technical University in Košice, Košice

2018 - 2021

## Continuation of previous field of study:

- deeper understanding of computer networks CCNA, CCNP introduction
- more in-depth software development courses

# Informačné a digitálne technológie, Súkromná stredná odborná škola Ul. 29. augusta, Poprad

September 2014 — June 2018

# A great introduction to everything IT:

· software development, networking, graphical design

# COURSES

# Cisco CCNA, Technical University in Košice

2020 - 2021

# RELEVANT SKILLS

# Working level programming understanding

I'm not a developer. But you're not looking for another developer. I have experience in working with Python, JS, Shell which to me proved sufficient to work and accurately write about complex technologies and processes.